http://www.jes-extender.com/staging_dev/sales-terms/

Order nowPenis ExtendersAccessoriesShipping policyPayment MethodsEffectsWho Can Use Jes ExtenderBigger and BetterStraightening Your PenisChordeeWhy Jes Extender Is The BestHow it WorksInstructional VideoPenis Enlargement MethodsStartup ProgramClinically TestedJes Extender ResultsMedical TestsThe Wendy Hurn StudyBJUI ResearchCE CertificateSupportQ&AMoney back guaranteeWarrantySupportAbout usContactTerms and ConditionsPayment MethodsShipping infoPrivacy policyBlog
Menu Order nowPenis ExtendersAccessoriesShipping policyPayment MethodsEffectsWho Can Use Jes ExtenderBigger and BetterStraightening Your PenisChordeeWhy Jes Extender Is The BestHow it WorksInstructional VideoPenis Enlargement MethodsStartup ProgramClinically TestedJes Extender ResultsMedical TestsThe Wendy Hurn StudyBJUI ResearchCE CertificateSupportQ&AMoney back guaranteeWarrantySupportAbout usContactTerms and ConditionsPayment MethodsShipping infoPrivacy policyBlog
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
The latest revision of these terms and conditions was 10.03.2020.JesExtender.com is owned and operated by DanaMedic ApS. Office hours are 8 AM to 4 PM (CET).DanaMedic ApS (VAT 12508670)Maglebjergvej 42800 Kgs. Lyngby, DenmarkPhone: +45 45 200 300Phone, EU and International: +44 11 5769 0221Phone, US and Canada: +1 646 569 9167PaymentDanaMedic ApS accepts online payments with the following credit cards: Dankort, Visa/Dankort, Visa, Mastercard, Visa Electron, Maestro, American Express, Diner’s, Paypal, Gpay and ApplePay.Payment will only be deducted from your account when the physical item is shipped. All prices on the website include VAT. The website uses the following primary currency for pricing: Euro (EUR)DanaMedic ApS uses a secure payment server that encrypts all information with SSL protocol, meaning your data is secure and cannot be read by other third parties. DanaMedic ApS’s own website also uses encryption with SSL protocol.Shipping policyDanaMedic ApS ships its products through professional and international couriers such as DHL Express, FEDEX, Deutsche Post, USPS and GLS at the earliest date and time possible.All orders received before noon (CET) on weekdays, will be shipped that same day.Estimated delivery time for EU customers is 24 hours, 1-2 days for US and Canada, and 3-4 days for the rest of the World. An e-mail with tracking number will be forwarded when the goods have been shipped.DanaMedic ApS ships to every country in the World at a flat rate of $19 to USA/Canada and €19 to EU. Quotes outside these countries depend on location and are shown in checkout.Note: As a special customer service we deliver to post boxes (PO Box) and army post boxes (APO’s), but in order to do so, are forced to make use of regular postal services, which leads to a significant increase in transit time – up to 14 business days.There may be unforeseen delays due to, for example, customs clearance, for which DanaMedic ApS cannot be held responsible. Similarly, DanaMedic ApS cannot be held responsible for import restrictions, duty, VAT or other costs for your country.If the product is returned to us, we will refund the full product price excluding shipping cost. Please read more in our Return Policy below.If the address typed on your order is incorrect, and consequently the product cannot be correctly delivered, DanaMedic ApS cannot be held responsible nor liable. Remember, we only have the data you type on your order to go by.DanaMedic ApS will do everything in our power to ship to the address you typed in checkout from our webshop: A total of three delivery attempts with email or text message will be undertaken to deliver the goods. In the unlikely event that all three attempts fail, the goods will be considered delivered, and a reimbursement on your behalf is forfeited.Revoking ordersAs a consumer you are entitled to a 14-day revoking period for goods purchased online. The 14-day period starts on the day the order is delivered.Please note the right of revocation on intimate products expires when opening the product packaging. If opened, our products unfortunately cannot be returned.The request for revocation must be notified to us no later than 14 days after the delivery.If you wish to make use of your right to revoke the purchase, you must either get in touch with our Chat through JesExtender.com or send us an e-mail at support@jes-extender.com. Clearly state in your message that you want to use your right of revocation.Return policyThere is a limited return policy, which means you can only return the product in agreement with our customer service if the product is of the same quality and condition as when you received it.For obvious hygienic reasons, the right of return of intimate products expires when opening the product packaging. Meaning you will lose the right of refund if you break the sealed plastic bag in which the product is delivered.This is clearly stated on the sealed bags as well as in our quickguide enclosed with the product. Unfortunately, we cannot refund a returned used product.The right of revocation will also automatically expire if you use the product in any way where the usage clearly reduces the sales value of the product.WarrantyThere is a 2-year warranty on products according to the Danish Sales Law. This warranty applies to errors in production and assembly of the product. Download the Jes-Extender warranty form. Money-back guaranteeWe guarantee that our product will give you an enlargement if used correctly and diligently. In fact, we offer you a refund if you get no results; If you haven’t enlarged your penis within 1,000 hours of training, you may apply for our money-back guarantee.The money-back guarantee can be claimed at any time during your first nine months with our product (only one refund per customer). All you need to do is enter your measurements every week in our diary at https://dickdiary.net to keep track of your progress.We kindly ask you to take a picture before and after the treatment, with the product applied, to make sure you have used it correctly. Please include a ruler placed on the penile column pointing towards the tip of the penis on both pictures.If you are ever without Internet access, simply let us know that you won’t be able to submit your results at that time.ComplaintsProduct errors and defects must be reported to DanaMedic ApS in a reasonable time after the goods have been received. We consider a maximum of 14 days as a reasonable time, unless otherwise agreed.The right to complaints is waived if the item is handled improperly or unusually. DanaMedic ApS covers return costs to a reasonable extent if the complaint is within warranty guidelines.When returning, please contact us at:DanaMedic ApSMaglebjergvej 42800 Kgs. Lyngby, Denmarksupport@jes-extender.comWarranty complaints will not be accepted if they are sent by cash-on-delivery system.Privacy PolicyWe do not resell personal information and do not pass on personal information to others. They are only registered in our customer directory. In accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation, you may delete your information at any time.For you to enter into an agreement with DanaMedic ApS, we need the following information:. Name. Full address. Phone number. Email addressWe make the registration of your personal information for the purpose of delivering the goods to you. The personal information is registered with DanaMedic ApS, and is stored for up to 5 years for corporate tax reasons after which the information is permanently deleted.When collecting personal information, we ensure it happens by submitting your explicit consent, so that you are informed exactly what information is being collected and why.The management and staff at DanaMedic ApS have access to your personal information. The responsible Data Manager for DanaMedic ApS is provided by Peytz & Co A/S.As registered with DanaMedic ApS, you always have the right to object to the registration. You also have the right to know what information is registered about you. You have these rights in the EU GDPR and in connection with this, please contact support@jes-extender.comCookiesOn JesExtender.com, cookies are used for the purpose of optimizing the website, and its functionality, making the visit as easy as possible for you. You can delete cookies from your computer at any time, see instructions on https://www.privacypolicies.com/blog/how-to-delete-cookies/AnalyticsWe use log statistics at the JesExtender website, which means, we have a statistics system, that gathers information to supply us with a statistical indication of how many visitors the site has, where they are from, and on which landing pages they leave the site and more. This is only used for the purpose of improving the JesExtender website.Consumer ProtectionLearn more about your consumer protection when paying online with PensoPay’s payment service solution: https://pensopay.com/en/more/consumer-protection/Official complaintsAny complaints pertaining to a product or service purchased from DanaMedic ApS may be submitted to the Danish Consumer Agency and Center for Klageløsning at:The Consumer Agency & Center for KlageløsningCarl Jacobsens Vej 352500 Valby, Denmarkhttps://www.forbrug.dkFor European citizens who reside outside of Europe, complaints must be submitted through the EU Commission Online Complaints Platform at https://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr/When filing an official complaint, you must file our email, support@jes-extender.com and JesExtender.com, where you made your purchase.In the event of a dispute, DanaMedic ApS will adhere to the Consumer Agency’s decision.
Terms and conditions
Privacy policy
Shipping policy Copyright © 2020. All Rights Reserved. Jes-Extender™ is owned and operated by DanaMedic ApS. DanaMedic ApS, VAT 12508670, Maglebjergvej 4, 2800 Kgs. Lyngby, Denmark Our business hours are weekdays, 8 AM to 4 PM (CET)Phone, Denmark: +45 45 200 300 Phone, US & Canada: +1 646 569 9167 Phone, EU & International: +44 115 769 0221
